This is what marriage feels like, by the
way. What it feels like in here.
Right now, it's just one person talking
and the other's like, "I'm going to get
out of here."
It's
That's
We I'm from Nashville, and uh me and my
wife, we were in Nashville last summer,
and we went out on the lake with some of
our friends, and we're like floating
around the water, and there's a guy in a
boat like right next to us, and my wife
was like, "Oh, that's my ex-boyfriend in
that boat."
Now, I didn't know who he was, so she
didn't have to say that at all, you
know?
She was just basically like, "You having
fun? Cuz I'd like to put a stop to
that."
And make you stare at this guy the rest
of the day.
So, I'm like staring at him, and then I
look at my wife, and she's staring at
him, and I feel like she's staring at
him to see what her life would be like
if she didn't marry me.
So, I started staring at him cuz I was
like, "I want to see what my life would
be like if I didn't marry her, you
know?"
And we were putting we were putting so
much pressure on this guy. And
we
we stared at him for a while, he did
nothing exciting at all. And uh you
know, we looked back at each other and
just realized, "You know what? We don't
have a boat. That's the only
difference."
My friends My friends were like, "You
should have went and tried to fight him.
Why don't you go fight him?"
And I was like, "Well, I would have had
to swim over to that fight."
So, I don't know how intimidating that
is for a guy to see a head in a life
jacket floating his way.
>> [laughter]
>> And then I got to get in the boat, you
know? Like, have you ever tried to climb
into a boat from water?
>> [laughter]
>> It's not aggressive.
It takes an hour if no one is in the
boat. Like
if he's in there, I'm never going to get
in. I would need his help. I'd be like,
"Could you help me into this boat?
I can't tell you why, but I really need
to be in this boat."